Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Faculty, 1955-1978
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1971 Apr (Folder 20.6)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1971 Oct (Folder 20.7)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1971 Dec (Folder 20.8)
  - Departmental Recommendations Book I — Anthropology-German, 1971 Dec (Folder 20.9)
  - Departmental Recommendations Book II — Hispanic Studies-East Asian Studies, 1971 Dec (Folder 20.10)
  - Recommendations for Reappointments, Promotions, and Terminations, 1972 Oct (Folder 20.11)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1972 Dec (Folder 20.12)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1974 Apr (Folder 20.13)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1974 Jul (Folder 20.14)
  - Departmental Recommendations — Faculty Review, 1974 Dec (Folder 20.15)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1975-1976 (Folder 20.16)
  - Departmental Recommendations — Faculty Review, 1975 Jul (Folder 20.17)
  - Departmental Recommendations — Faculty Review, 1975 Dec (Folder 20.18)
  - Faculty Reviews, 1976 Jul (Folder 20.19)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1976 Mar (Folder 20.20)
  - Faculty Budget — Work Copy, 1976-1977 (Folder 20.21)
  - Faculty Salary Budget — Final Copy, 1976-1977 (Folder 20.22)
  - Faculty Reviews, 1976-1977 (Folder 21.1)
  - Faculty Salary Recommendations — Book I, 1976-1977 (Folder 21.2)
  - Faculty Salary Recommendations — Book II, 1976-1977 (Folder 21.3)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1964-1966 (Folder 21.4)
  - Development Group, 1959-1965 (Folder 21.5)
  - Development Group Minutes, 1959-1962 (Folder 21.6)
  - Development Group — W-12, 1961-1966 (Folder 21.7)
  - Governance Revision — Faculty Housing, 1960-1966 (Folder 21.8)
  - Committee on Fellowships and Graduate Study, 1960-1966 (Folder 21.9)
  - Adloff Lecture, 1964 (Folder 21.10)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1960-1966 (Folder 21.11)
  - Committee on Library, 1957-1966 (Folder 21.12)
  - Faculty Mellon Committee, 1963-1964 (Folder 21.13)
  - Faculty Committee on the Mellon Fund, 1962-1966 (Folder 21.14)
  - Committee on Selection of President (Folder 21.15)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1960-1962 (Folder 21.16)
  - Committee on Research, 1959-1964 (Folder 21.17)
  - Committee on Research, 1964-1965 (Folder 21.18)
  - Committee on Scholarships, 1959-1966 (Folder 21.19)
  - Scholarships — Difficulties with Vassar Clubs, 1962-1963 (Folder 21.20)
  - Committee on Students’ Records, 1960-1962 (Folder 22.1)
  - Committee on Teacher Training, 1959-1964 (Folder 22.2)
  - Committee on Teacher Education — Five College Project, 1963-1966 (Folder 22.3)
  - Committee on Teacher Education, 1964-1965 (Folder 22.4)
  - Committee on Teacher Education (Candidates for Director), 1965 (Folder 22.5)
  - Committee on Teacher Education (Charles Keller’s papers), 1965-1966 (Folder 22.6)
  - Committee on Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies, 1955-1966 (Folder 22.7)
  - Committee on Committees, 1959-1964 (Folder 22.8)
  - Committee on Conference with the Trustees, 1959-1966 (Folder 22.9)
  - Committee on Convocation, 1959-1966 (Folder 22.10)
  - Coordinating Committee on Educational Policy, 1958 Oct (Folder 22.11)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1959-1961 (Folder 22.12)
  - Faculty (General), 1955-1966 (Folder 22.13)
  - Advisory Committee, 1959-1965 (Folder 22.14)
  - Faculty Club, 1959-1964 (Folder 22.15)
  - Secretary of the Faculty, 1961-1966 (Folder 22.16)
  - Administrative Council Minutes, 1959-1966 (Folder 22.17)
  - Department Chairmen, 1960-1966 (Folder 22.18)
  - Commencement, 1959-1964 (Folder 22.19)
  - History of the Vassar Curriculum 1915-1965 (Folder 22.20)
  - Faculty — General, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.21)
  - Secretary of Faculty, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.22)
  - Faculty Club, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.23)
  - Department Chairmen, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.24)
  - Administrative Council, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.25)
  - Advisory Committee, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.26)
  - Committee on Committees, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.27)
  - Committee on Conference with the Trustees, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.28)
  - Committee on Convocation, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.29)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.30)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1967-1968 (Folder 22.31)
  - Development Group — W-12, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.32)
  - Development Group Minutes, 1966 (Folder 22.33)
  - Dormitory Planning Committee, 1967-1968 (Folder 22.34)
  - Committee on Revision of Faculty By-Laws, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.35)
  - Environmental Studies, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.36)
  - GDL — Vassar’s Developing Interest in Environmental Studies, 1966-1967 (Folder 22.37)
  - GDL — Environmental Studies Folder: Suggestions and Advice from Consultants and Vassar Faculty, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.38)
  - GDL — Environmental Studies Folder: Proposals, 1966-1968 (Folder 22.39)
  - Committee on Environmental Studies, 1966 (Folder 22.40)
  - Committee on Faculty Housing, 1968 (Folder 22.41)
  - Committee on Fellowships and Graduate Study, 1966-1968 (Folder 23.1)
  - Committee on Fellowships, (empty) (Folder 23.2)
  - Committee on Revision of the Governance, 1960-1962 (Folder 23.3)
  - Revision of Governance, 1961-1962 (Folder 23.4)
  - Revision of Governance, 1963-1965 (Folder 23.5)
  - Governance Revision — Miscellaneous Copies, 1962-1965 (Folder 23.6)
  - Revised Government — Draft (Folder 23.7)
  - Governance Revision, 1965 (Folder 23.8)
  - Governance (Material circulated to Faculty), 1965 (Folder 23.9)
  - Governance Committee, 1965-1970 (Folder 23.10)
  - Committee on Foreign Study, 1966-1967; (empty) (Folder 23.11)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, 1968 (Folder 23.12)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1966-1968 (Folder 23.13)
  - Committee on the Mellon Fund, 1966-1967 (Folder 23.14)
  - Committee on Privileges in Elections, 1968 (Folder 23.15)
  - Committee on Research, 1966-1968 (Folder 23.16)
  - Committee on Research (Leaves Policies and Cost), 1965-1966 (Folder 23.17)
  - Committee on Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Folder 23.18)
  - Steering Committee, 1967-1968 (Folder 23.19)
  - Committee on Students’ Records, 1967 (Folder 23.20)
  - Committee on Five-College Project, 1966-1968 (Folder 23.21)
  - Committee on Teacher Education, 1966-1968 (Folder 23.22)
  - Committee on Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies, 1966-1967 (Folder 23.23)
  - Sub-Committee on Athletic Facilities, 1968-1969 (Folder 23.24)
  - Committee on Black Studies, 1968-1970 (Folder 23.25)
  - Committee on Revision of By-Laws, 1969 (Folder 23.26)
  - Commencement, 1969 (Folder 23.27)
  - Commencement, 1970 (Folder 24.1)
  - Committee on Committees, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.2)
  - Comprehensive Planning Committee, 1968 (Folder 24.3)
  - Comprehensive Plan Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 24.4)
  - Committee on Conference with the Trustees, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.5)
  - Committee on Convocation, 1968-1969 (Folder 24.6)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.7)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 24.8)
  - Committee on Faculty Housing, 1969 (Folder 24.9)
  - Committee on Faculty Procedure, 1969-1970 (Folder 24.10)
  - Committee on Fellowships, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.11)
  - Committee on Foreign Study, 1968-1970; (empty) (Folder 24.12)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.13)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.14)
  - Committee for Master Planning, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.15)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1969-1970 (Folder 24.16)
  - Committee on Records and Honors, 1969 (Folder 24.17)
  - Committee on Privileges in Elections, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.18)
  - Faculty — General, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.19)
  - Secretary of Faculty, 1968-1969 (Folder 24.20)
  - Faculty Club, 1969-1970 (Folder 24.21)
  - Department Chairmen, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.22)
  - Advisory Committee, 1968-1970 (Folder 24.23)
  - Committee on Research Grants-in-Aid, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.1)
  - Committee on Research (Leave Policies and Cost), 1968-1970 (Folder 25.2)
  - Committee on Research, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.3)
  - Documents Relating to New Leave Policy, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.4)
  - Faculty Leave Policy, 1969 (Folder 25.5)
  - Committee on Research, 1969-1970 (Folder 25.6)
  - W. K. Rose Fellowship Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 25.7)
  - Committee on Scholarships, 1969 (Folder 25.8)
  - Committee on Social Action, 1968-1970 (Folder 25.9)
  - Steerling Committee, 1968 (Folder 25.10)
  - Committee on Students’ Records, 1969 (Folder 25.11)
  - Committee on Five-College Project, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.12)
  - Committee on Teacher Education — Implementation of MAT Programs, 1967-1968 (Folder 25.13)
  - Committee on Teacher Education, 1968-1970 (Folder 25.14)
  - Certification Application for MAT Program, 1968 (Folder 25.15)
  - MAT Program, 1968 (Folder 25.16)
  - Committee on Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies, 1969 (Folder 25.17)
  - Committee on Work Load, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.18)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1969 Feb (Folder 25.19)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.20)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1968-1969 (Folder 25.21)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1969-1970 (Folder 25.22)
  - Secretary of Faculty, 1970-1974 (Folder 25.23)
  - Department Chairmen, 1970-1973 (Folder 25.24)
  - Academic Panel, 1970 (Folder 25.25)
  - Advisory Committee, 1970-1972 (Folder 25.26)
  - Appointments and Salary Committee, 1971-1973 (Folder 25.27)
  - Tenure Cases — Faculty Appointments Committee, 1972 (Folder 25.28)
  - Faculty Appointments Committee — Tenure Decisions, 1973 (Folder 25.29)
  - Tenure — Other Decisions, 1973 (Folder 25.30)
  - Appointments and Salary Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 25.31)
  - Ad Hoc Faculty Salary Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 25.32)
  - Faculty Salary Material and Faculty Salary Budget, 1973 (Folder 25.33)
  - Tenure and other Decisions, 1974 Jul 1 (Folder 25.34)
  - Tenure Review Material and Other Decisions, 1972-1973 (Folder 25.35)
  - Faculty Appointments and Salary Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 26.1)
  - Faculty Committee on Black Studies, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.2)
  - Commencement, 1971 (Folder 26.3)
  - Commencement, 1972 (Folder 26.4)
  - Commencement, 1973 (Folder 26.5)
  - Commencement, 1974 (Folder 26.6)
  - Committee on Committees, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.7)
  - Committee on Committees, 1971-1973 (Folder 26.8)
  - Committee on Conference with the Trustees, 1971-1972 (Folder 26.9)
  - Committee on Convocation, 1970-1972 (Folder 26.10)
  - Committee on Convocation, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.11)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1971-1972 (Folder 26.12)
  - Committee on Curricular Policy, 1972-1973 (Folder 26.13)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.14)
  - Committee on Faculty Housing, 1970-1972 (Folder 26.15)
  - Committee on Faculty Procedure, 1971-1972 (Folder 26.16)
  - Committee on Fellowships, 1970-1974 (Folder 26.17)
  - Committee on Financial Planning, 1970-1971 (Folder 26.18)
  - Governance Committee, 1969-1971 (Folder 26.19)
  - Governance Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 26.20)
  - Governance Revision, 1971 (Folder 26.21)
  - Governance Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.22)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1970-1972 (Folder 26.23)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.24)
  - Committee for Master Planning, 1970-1972 (Folder 26.25)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1970-1972 (Folder 26.26)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1972-1973 (Folder 26.27)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.28)
  - Faculty Committee on Policy and Conference — Budgetary Proposals, 1973-1974 (Folder 26.29)
  - Committee on Research, 1970-1974 (Folder 26.30)
  - Committee on Research Grants-in-Aid, 1970-1972 (Folder 26.31)
  - W.K. Rose Fellowship Committee, 1971-1974 (Folder 26.32)
  - Committee of Seven, 1971 (Folder 26.33)
  - Committee on Student Life (Folder 26.34)
  - Committee on Student Records, 1972 (Folder 26.35)
  - Committee on Teacher Education, 1970 (Folder 26.36)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1976-1977 (Folder 26.37)
  - Faculty — General, 1972-1976 (Folder 26.38)
  - Secretary of the Faculty, 1974-1977 (Folder 26.39)
  - Faculty Meeting — Index of Minutes (Folder 26.40)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1976-1977 (Folder 26.41)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1975-1976 (Folder 26.42)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1974-1975 (Folder 26.43)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1976 May (Folder 26.44)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1976 Apr (Folder 27.1)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1975 Mar-May (Folder 27.2)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1975 Dec (Folder 27.3)
  - Faculty Meeting and F.P.C., 1973 Mar (Folder 27.4)
  - Committee on Committees, 1974-1977 (Folder 27.5)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1974-1975 (Folder 27.6)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1975-1976 (Folder 27.7)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1976 (Folder 27.8)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1977 (Folder 27.9)
  - Energy Conservation Committee, 1975 (Folder 27.10)
  - Faculty Appointments and Salary Material, 1975-1976 (Folder 27.11)
  - Faculty Appointments and Salary Committee — Faculty Reviews, 1976-1977 (Folder 27.12)
  - Faculty and Student Budget Review Committee (Short Term Financial Planning), 1976-1977 (Folder 27.13)
  - Faculty-Student Budget Review Committee, 1976 (Folder 27.14)
  - Committee on Faculty Procedure, 1975-1976 (Folder 27.15)
  - Committee on Fellowships, 1974-1977 (Folder 27.16)
  - Committee on Governance, 1974; (empty) (Folder 27.17)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1974-1977 (Folder 27.18)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1975-1976 (Folder 27.19)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1976-1977 (Folder 27.20)
  - Committee on Policy and Conference, 1974-1975 (Folder 27.21)
  - Committee on Research, 1974-1977 (Folder 27.22)
  - W.K. Rose Fellowship Committee, 1974-1977 (Folder 27.23)
  - Committee on Status of Women, 1974-1976 (Folder 27.24)
  - Committee on Status of Women at Vassar, 1970-1978 (Folder 27.24a)
  - Current Faculty, 1964-1965 (Folder 27.25)
  - Contracts, 1964-1965 (Folder 27.26)
  - Current Faculty, 1965-1966 (Folder 27.27)
  - Contracts, 1965-1966 (Folder 27.28)
  - Current Faculty, 1966-1967 (Folder 27.29)
  - Contracts, 1966-1967 (Folder 27.30)
  - Current Faculty, 1967-1968 (Folder 28.1)
  - Contracts, 1967-1968 (Folder 28.2)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.3)
  - Candidates for Deanship, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.4)
  - House Fellows, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.5)
  - Recorder, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.6)
  - Recorder — Faculty/Student Ratios of Vassar, 1964-1965 (Folder 28.7)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.8)
  - Dean of Studies, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.9)
  - Director of Scholarship and Financial Aid, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.10)
  - Study Counselor, 1965 (Folder 28.11)
  - Dean of Residence, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.12)
  - Committee on Admission, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.13)
  - Library — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.14)
  - Art — Applicants, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.15)
  - Art — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.16)
  - Biological Sciences, 1963-1965 (Folder 28.17)
  - Biology — Applicants, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.18)
  - Biology — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.19)
  - Chemistry — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.20)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.21)
  - Classics — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.22)
  - Hallie Flanagan Davis, 1965 (Folder 28.23)
  - Drama — Visiting Committee, 1965 (Folder 28.24)
  - Drama — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.25)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Applicants, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.26)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.27)
  - English — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.28)
  - English — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.29)
  - French — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.30)
  - French — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.31)
  - Geology and Geography — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.32)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.33)
  - German — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.34)
  - Health — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.35)
  - Health — Psychiatrist, 1965-1977 (Folder 28.36)
  - History — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.37)
  - History — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.38)
  - Italian — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.39)
  - Italian — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.40)
  - Mathematics — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.41)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.42)
  - Music — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.43)
  - Music — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.44)
  - Chaplain, 1966 (Folder 28.45)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.46)
  - Philosophy — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.47)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.48)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.49)
  - Physics — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.50)
  - Physics — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.51)
  - Political Science — Applicants, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.52)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.53)
  - Psychology — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.54)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.55)
  - Religion — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.56)
  - Russian — Applicants, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.57)
  - Russian — Officers, 1966 (Folder 28.58)
  - Spanish — Applicants, 1966 (Folder 28.59)
  - Spanish — Officers, 1965-1966 (Folder 28.60)
  - Dean of Residence, 1966-1969 (Folder 29.1)
  - Chaplain, 1966-1967 (Folder 29.2)
  - Chaplain — Applicants, 1964-1967; (4 folders) (Folder 29.3)
  - Dan of Faculty, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.4)
  - Dean of the Faculty Elect (Mrs. Eurich), 1966-1968 (Folder 29.5)
  - Dean of the Faculty (Mrs. Eurich), 1967-1968 (Folder 29.6)
  - Candidate for Deanship of the Faculty, 1966 (Folder 29.7)
  - Studies by Mrs. Divina, 1968 (Folder 29.8)
  - House Fellows, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.9)
  - Recorder Candidates, 1967 (Folder 29.10)
  - Recorder, 1968 (Folder 29.11)
  - Dean of Studies, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.12)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1967-1968 (Folder 29.13)
  - Director of Scholarship and Financial Aid, 1966-1967 (Folder 29.14)
  - Study Counselor, 1967-1968 (Folder 29.15)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.16)
  - Committee on Admission, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.17)
  - Admissions and A.A.V.C., 1965-1966 (Folder 29.18)
  - Library — Applicants, 1966-1967 (Folder 29.19)
  - Library — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.20)
  - Art — Applicants, 1968 (Folder 29.21)
  - Art Catalogue, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.22)
  - Art — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.23)
  - Biology — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.24)
  - Biology — Chairmanship, Curriculum, Building Plans, 1965-1966 (Folder 29.25)
  - Biology — Officers, 1967-1968 (Folder 29.26)
  - Chemistry — Applicants, 1968 (Folder 29.27)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.28)
  - Classics — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.29)
  - Drama — Applicants, 1966-1967 (Folder 29.30)
  - Drama — Visiting Committee, 1966 (Folder 29.31)
  - Drama — Officers, 1967-1968 (Folder 29.32)
  - Economics, Sociology, Anthropology — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.33)
  - English — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.34)
  - English — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.35)
  - French — Applicants, 1967 (Folder 29.36)
  - French — Officers, 1967-1968 (Folder 29.37)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1967-1968 (Folder 29.38)
  - German — Applicants, 1966-1967 (Folder 29.39)
  - German — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.40)
  - Health — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.41)
  - Symposium on the Psychology of Student Protest, 1966 Nov (Folder 29.42)
  - Health —Psychiatrist, 1966 (Folder 29.43)
  - Review of College Health Service, 1966-1967 (Folder 29.44)
  - Health — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.45)
  - History — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.46)
  - History — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 29.47)
  - Italian — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.1)
  - Mathematics — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.2)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.3)
  - Music — Applicants, 1968 (Folder 30.4)
  - Music — Madrigal Singers Tour, 1967-1968 (Folder 30.5)
  - Philosophy — Applicants, 1968 (Folder 30.6)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.7)
  - Physical Education Officers, 1967-1968 (Folder 30.8)
  - Physics — Applicants, 1967 (Folder 30.9)
  - Physics — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.10)
  - Political Science — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.11)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.12)
  - Psychology — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.13)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.14)
  - Religion — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.15)
  - Russian — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.16)
  - Russian — Officers, 1968 (Folder 30.17)
  - Spanish — Applicants, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.18)
  - Spanish — Officers, 1966-1968 (Folder 30.19)
  - Committee on the Chaplaincy, 1970 (Folder 30.20)
  - Chaplain, 1968-1969 (Folder 30.21)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1968-1969 (Folder 30.22)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1969-1970 (Folder 30.23)
  - Acting Dean of Faculty — Miss Marion Tait, 1970 (Folder 30.24)
  - Assistant to Dean of Faculty — Charles Griffin, 1969-1970 (Folder 30.25)
  - Committee on Deanship, 1970 (Folder 30.26)
  - House Fellows, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.27)
  - Recorder, 1969-1970 (Folder 30.28)
  - Recorder Candidates, 1969-1970 (Folder 30.29)
  - Vice President of Student Affairs, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.30)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Reports to Trustees, 1969-1970 (Folder 30.31)
  - Mr. Dwight Chapman Studies (Coeducation), 1969-1970 (Folder 30.32)
  - Dean of Studies, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.33)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.34)
  - Director of Financial Aid, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.35)
  - Dean of Residence, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.36)
  - Admission Office — Applicants, 1968-1969 (Folder 30.37)
  - Director of Admissions (Mr. Stephenson), 1969-1970 (Folder 30.38)
  - Committee on Admission, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.39)
  - Admissions, 1967-1968 (Folder 30.40)
  - Vassar ‘68, 1968 (Folder 30.41)
  - Library — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.42)
  - Sociology-Anthropology — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.43)
  - Art — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.44)
  - Springside, 1968-1969 (Folder 30.45)
  - Art Gallery, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.46)
  - Art — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 30.47)
  - Biology — Applicants, 1968-1969 (Folder 31.1)
  - Biology — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.2)
  - Chemistry — Applicants, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.3)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.4)
  - Classics — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.5)
  - Drama — Applicants, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.6)
  - Drama — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.7)
  - Economics — Applicants, 1970 (Folder 31.8)
  - Economics — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.9)
  - English — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.10)
  - English — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.11)
  - French — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.12)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.13)
  - German — Officers, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.14)
  - Health — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.15)
  - Health — Psychiatrist, 1968-1969 (Folder 31.16)
  - Review of College Health Service, 1970 (Folder 31.17)
  - Health — Officers, 1968-1969 (Folder 31.18)
  - Hispanic Studies — Applicants, 1969 (Folder 31.19)
  - Hispanic Studies — Officers, 1969 (Folder 31.20)
  - History — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.21)
  - History — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.22)
  - Italian — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.23)
  - Mathematics — Applicants, 1970 (Folder 31.24)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.25)
  - Music — Applicants, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.26)
  - Music — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.27)
  - Philosophy — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.28)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.29)
  - Physical Education — Applicants, 1969 (Folder 31.30)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.31)
  - Physics-Astronomy — Applicants, 1969 (Folder 31.32)
  - Physics-Astronomy — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.33)
  - Political Science — Applicants, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.34)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1968-1969 (Folder 31.35)
  - Psychology — Applicants, 1969-1970 (Folder 31.36)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1968-1970 (Folder 31.37)
  - Religion — Applicants, 1969 (Folder 31.38)